Narrator: Speaker 1
Speaker 1: …the house where we are now,
I drive east into the sun in the morning to get to work
and west into the sun in the evening to get home.
So, today, like every sunny day now, I have to half-close my eyes to drive,
I’m squinting all the way there for 40 minutes, and the same on the way home…
Narrator: Speaker 2
Speaker 2: …so as soon as I realized it actually was him, I immediately turned away,
and then I glanced at him again just to make completely sure,
and took another peek to see who he was with.
I think it was his wife and maybe his agent or something.
I texted my brother who’s a real fan, and he wanted me to go up and say hello,
but I wouldn’t have dreamed of doing that…
Narrator: Speaker 3
Speaker 3: …I mean, you would think nowadays everybody knows
how rude it is to talk loudly on your phone on public transport.
So, I stared hard at him to see if he’d get the message, but he didn’t.
Then, a few minutes later, he caught my eye and I just glared,
and though he didn’t hang up, at least he started speaking a bit more quietly…
Narrator: Speaker 4
Speaker 4: …and after crawling along in the traffic for a bit,
we noticed that there was a car on fire by the side of the road,
and, would you believe it, instead of just driving past,
everyone was slowing down and gawping at the fire engine
and the ambulance and everything…
Narrator: Speaker 5
Speaker 5: …so I was pretty late anyway, but she wasn’t there when I got there,
so I looked around and I caught a glimpse of her red coat.
She was walking away down the road, so I ran after her, shouting ‘Gill! Gill!’,
and got right up behind her and she turned around, and it wasn’t her!
She just gave me a blank stare. So embarrassing.